

### **Contact**



0750 323 9373



Kotr City, Erbil



muhammadkhalilsalih@gmail.com

### **Education**

- Information Technology Shaqlawa Technical Collage 2022 - 2024
- Electrical for Houses
  Islamic Relief
  2019 2Months
- Life Skills
   Islamic Relief
   2019 6days

### Skill

- Communication Skill
- Html
- Css
- Php
- C#
- Microsoft Office
  - (Word, Excel, Powerpoint)
- Windows-Os , Kali Linux-Os
- Fast typing

# Muhammad Khalil Salih

## **About Me**

I am an expert Electrical Technician with a strong background in residential electrical systems and a passion for renewable energy solutions. My technical expertise extends to solar panel installations that enhance energy efficiency for clients and Camera installations. In addition to my practical experience, I hold certifications in Kali Linux, Electrical Technician, and Life Skills.

# Experience

### Electrical: Erbil & Around of Erbil

2019-2022

After completing the course provided by Islamic Relief, I started working and improved my skills in residential electrical installations.

#### Solar Panel: Erbil & Around Of Erbil

2021-2022

I Have Also Start Working And More Improving Myself By Connecting Of Solar Panel For (Houses, Storages..etc), That Made Me More Efficient.

#### Camera: Erbil & Around Of Erbil

2021-2022

I Have Also Start Working And More Improving Myself By Installation Of Camera For (Houses, Storages..etc), That Made Me More Efficient.

# Language

**Kurdish** — Native Language

#### Other Language(s):

English — Listening A2 — Reading A2 — Wrinting A2

**Arabic** — Listening A1 — Reading A1 — Wrinting A1